잠깐만, 들어가기 전에
사랑한다는 말을 해주고 싶어
Wait. Before we go in, I just
want you to know that I love you.
신혼 여행은 정말 환상적이었어
I had a great time on our honeymoon.
앞으로의 결혼 생활이 기대가 돼
I can't wait
to spend our life together.
조개 목걸이 안 버렸네?
You're sticking with
the shell necklace, huh?
왔구나!
You're back!
들어와!
Come on in!
신혼 여행은 어땠어?
How was the honeymoon?
정말 재밌었어, 거기다가
멋진 부부를 만났지 뭐야
So much fun. The best part is,
we met this great couple.
그게 그렇게 대단해?
별 이상한 신혼 여행도 다 있네
That was the best part?
Good honeymooning, tiger.
얼마나 좋은 사람들인데
그쪽도 신혼 여행 온 거였어
They're cool.
It was their honeymoon too.
게다가 여기에 산대
They live here in the city.
전화해볼까? 너무 일러?
전화하고 싶어
Can we go call them?
Is it too soon to call?
너무 신나, 함께 어울릴
커플을 마침내 찾았거든
We're excited. We finally
have a couple to hang out with.
커플을 찾고 있었어?
Oh, were you looking for that?
그럼
Well, yeah.
커플? 그러니까 두 사람?
한 사람, 두 사람?
A couple? Like two people?
Like one, two people?
이건 달라, 그렉과 제니는
결혼한 부부라구
It's different.
Greg and Jenny are married.
그렉과 제니?
"안녕 그렉, 나 챈들러야"
Greg and Jenny?
"Hi, Greg. I'm Chandler."
"안녕 모니카, 나 제니야"
"안녕 제니, 안녕 그렉"
"Hi, Monica. This is Jenny."
"Hi, Jenny. Hi, Greg."
- 멋진 사람들이야, 기회를...
- 기회고 뭐고
-They're great. If you just..
-You know what?
기념품이나 내놓고 당장 꺼져
Give us our souvenirs
and get out of here.
- 기념품 살 틈이...
- 농담 작작 해!
-We didn't get a chance to..
-You're kidding!
- 아무 것도 못 샀어
- 목걸이 좋네
-We didn't get anything for anyone.
-Nice necklace.
너 가져
That you can have.
프렌즈 시즌 8
'증거 테이프'
- 잘 왔어
- 신혼 여행은 어땠어?
-Welcome home.
-How was the honeymoon?
좋았어! 두 사람은 어때?
엄마 아빠가 되는 거잖아!
Great! How about you?
You're having a baby!
그래, 아주 신나
Yeah, we are. It's so exciting.
두 사람이 사생아 낳을 줄
진작에 알고 있었어
I always knew you two
would have a child out of wedlock.
- 아기 초음파 사진 보여줄게
- 좋아
-Look, I have a sonogram picture.
-Good.
로스, 눈썹이 진하게
꿈틀거리는 게 너랑 똑같아
Ross, it's got your wavy, black lines.
좋아, 이제 로스도 아니까 말해봐
언제였어? 몇 번이나 했어?
Now that Ross knows, how'd it happen?
When? How many times?
모니카, 그건 옳지 않아
어디서였는지부터 말해
Monica, that's not right.
Start with where.
6주 전이었을 거야
It happened about six weeks ago.
집에 왔는데 로스가 있더라구
조이랑 어울려 다닐 때였거든
I got home and Ross was there.
He'd been hanging out with Joey.
고맙긴, 친구
You're welcome, buddy.
맞아, 고마워
Yeah, thanks.
할 일이 아주 많았는데
로스가 돕겠다고 하더라구
I had a lot of work,
and Ross offered to help.
와인을 마시며 얘기를 했는데
We had wine, we got to talking.
문득 보니
로스가 다가와있는 거야
Next thing you know,
Ross comes on to me.
그건 좀 아니네
That's a little misleading.
- 뭐가?
- 거짓말이잖아
-What is?
-The lie you just told.
- 네가 다가온 거?
- 그래, 그거!
-That you came on to me?
-There's the one!
- 사실이잖아, 우리 솔직해져
- 그래, 솔직해져
-But you did. Let's be honest.
-Yes, let's.
로스, 도움이 될까 해서
하는 말인데 난 너 안 믿어
Ross. If it helps, I don't believe you.
그건 중요하지 않아
It's not important.
중요한 건 아기를 낳는다는 거지
누가 누굴 유혹했든 상관없잖아
What's important is, we're having
a baby, not who came on to who.
'누구를'이지
"Whom."
옳은 말씀이야
That's right.
- 네가 먼저 키스했어
- 해달라고 통 사정했잖아!
-You kissed me first.
-You were begging for it!
신호를 마구 보낸 건 너였다구!
You were sending me signals!
신호를 보내? 내가 로스한테
신호 보낼 사람이라고 생각하는 분?
I was sending signals? Anyone think
that I'd send Ross begging signals?
손 들어봐
Please, show of hands.
사람들 생각은 중요하지 않아!
엄연히 있었던 사실이라구
It doesn't matter what people believe!
It happened.
이제부턴 조심해야겠네
지금도 내가 신호 보내고 있어?
Maybe I need to be more careful.
Am I sending these signals now?
- 됐어, 관두자
- 내가 어떻게 애걸했나 보여줘봐
-You know what? Just drop it.
-Show me how I begged you.
보여달라면 보여주지!
비디오에 다 녹화돼있어
I can show you!
I have it on videotape.
말이 그렇다는 거지
It's an expression.
문 좀 열어, 할 말이 있단 말야
Come on, Rachel, open up.
Let me explain.
- 아직도구나?
- 그래
-Still won't let you in, huh?
-No.
이 문 닫을게, 네 얘기할 거거든
I'm just gonna close this door
so we can talk about you.
섹스하는 걸 찍다니
믿을 수가 없어
I can't believe
he taped them having sex.
그러게, 상대방한테
얘길 하고 찍었어야지
Yeah. You gotta tell a girl
before you tape her.
초보라 저지른 실수야
Such a rookie mistake.
- 그 사람들 카메라 끝내주지?
- 그렉이랑 제니?
-Know who has a great camera?
-Greg and Jenny?
- 전화해볼까? 하고 싶어
- 좋아
-I want to call them.
-Let's call.
그쪽은 친구들한테 줄
기념품 사왔는지 물어봐
Ask them if they brought
their friends souvenirs.
여보세요? 8번가 델리요?
Hello. 8th Street Deli?
끊어, 거기랑은 대화만 해도
식중독에 걸린단 말야
Hang up. You get food poisoning
just talking to that place.
- 미안해요, 잘못 걸었어요
- 여깄어
-Sorry, wrong number.
-Here you go, babe.
여보세요? 또 그 델리야!
Hello?
It's the deli again!
알았어, 난 샌드위치 먹을게
All right, I'll have a sandwich.
번호가 틀린가 봐
I don't think this number's right.
- 왜 그래?
- 틀린 번호를 준 거야
-What?
-You got fake-numbered.
- 뭐? 그런 짓은 아무도 안 해
- 우린 해
-What? People don't do that.
-Oh, I think we do.
- 그 사람들이 왜 그러겠어?
- 그러게 말야
-Why would they do that?
-I don't know.
자기가 얼마나 멋졌는데
좋은 질문만 골라서 했다구
You were a delight.
You asked those great questions.
자긴 또 얼마나 재밌었는데
유머, 유머, 유머! 끝내줬다구!
And you were never funnier.
Joke, joke, joke! You were a hoot!
걱정 마, 나랑 피비가 있잖아
You still got me and Phoebe.
됐어, 그렉이랑 제니가
버린 건 나도 싫어
Excuse me, I don't want
Greg and Jenny's rejects.
나랑 말도 안 하려고 해
문도 안 열어준다구
Rachel won't talk to me.
She won't open the door.
당연하지, 변태
I wonder why, pervert.
난 변태가 아냐
Okay, I am not a pervert.
변태들은 다 그런 말하더라
That's, like, the pervert motto.
오른손 올리고 왼손으로
바지 내리면서 그 말 다시 해봐
You raise your hand, put your left
hand down your pants and repeat that.
의도적으로 촬영한 게 아니었어
Filming Rachel was not planned.
어떻게 된 건지 설명을 해줄게
조이가 내 증인이야
Here's what happened.
Joey can back me up.
한 달 반 전에 내가 뭐 상의하러
찾아왔던 거 기억나?
A month and a half ago, remember
I came to you with a problem?
개인적인 문제로?
The personal thing?
- 무슨 개인적인 문제?
- 섹스에 대한 거?
-What personal thing?
-About sex?
몇 달 동안 섹스 못했다고 한 거?
That I hadn't had sex in months?
일부러 기억 안 나는 척한 거야
Yeah, I knew what
you were talking about.
'6주 전'
시간 있으면 나랑
입 밖에 꺼내기 어색한 얘기 좀 해
I'd like to talk about something
I'm uncomfortable talking about.
그래
Sure.
네가 엄마랑 샤워하는 얘기 어때?
How about you showering
with your mom?
할 얘긴 내가 뽑아왔어
I actually had a topic in mind.
사실 나 가뭄을 겪고 있어
섹스 가뭄 말야
I'm kind of going through
a dry spell, sex-wise.
- 얼마 동안이나?
- 5개월, 아니...
-For, like, months?
-Five, to be..
사실은 6개월이야
lying. Six.
6개월? 힘들겠네
Six months? That's rough.
꼭 그렇진 않아, 덕분에 작은 일에
감사하는 법을 배웠거든
It's not all bad. I'm learning to
appreciate the small things, like..
가령 새 울음소리라든가
하늘 색 같은 거 말야
the sound of a bird
and the color of the sky.
하늘은 파래, 난 어제 섹스했다구
The sky's blue, Ross.
And I had sex yesterday.
제발 나 좀 도와줘
오늘밤에 데이트가 있어
Please help me.
I have a date tonight.
꼭 성공해야 된단 말야
내 건강이 염려돼
It has to go well.
I'm scared for my health.
내가 여자들 관심을 끌고 싶을 때
써먹는 얘기가 있는데
I got something.
It's this story that I came up with.
아주 낭만적이야
여자들이 다 넘어오지
Very romantic.
Any woman that hears it is putty.
얘기해봐
Tell it to me.
이걸 들으면 네가 나랑
섹스하고 싶어질 거야
Now, you're gonna want to have sex
with me when you hear it.
이건 이야기일 뿐이란 걸 명심해
Remember, it is just the story.
자제하도록 노력할게
I'll try to control myself.
오래 전 내가 서유럽으로
배낭 여행을 간 적이 있어
Years ago, I was backpacking
across Western Europe..
- 네가 유럽으로 배낭 여행을?
- 앞으로 6개월 재밌게 보내
-You were backpacking across Europe?
-Have a nice six more months.
미안해, 이렇게 부탁할게
서유럽에 갔는데 뭐?
I'm sorry. Please, please.
You were in Western Europe, and..?
바르셀로나 교외에 있는
티비다보 산을 오르고 있었지
I was outside Barcelona, hiking
in the foothills of Mount Tibidabo.
- 멋있어
- 고마워
-Nice.
-Thanks.
산길을 벗어나자 호수가 보이더군
I was at the end of this path,
and there was a lake.
아주 외딴 곳이었어
주변엔 나무 말곤 없었지
Very secluded.
There were tall trees all around.
적막만이 흐르는데 아름다웠어
It was dead silent.
Gorgeous.
그때 호수 저편에 예쁜 여자가
혼자 목욕을 하고 있는 거야
And across the lake I saw
a beautiful woman bathing herself.
울면서 말야
But she was crying.
왜?
Why?
포도주가 좋은데요
This is great wine.
원산지가 프랑스죠
It's from France.
유럽에 있는...
In Europe.
서유럽이오
Western Europe.
몇 년 전 서유럽으로
배낭 여행을 간 적이 있어요
A few years ago I was backpacking
across Western Europe.
- 정말요?
- 기다려요, 더 재밌어져요
-Really?
-Wait, it gets better.
바르셀로나에 갔는데...
Yeah, I was in Barcelona.
바르셀로나에서 1년 유학했어요
I studied for a year in Barcelona.
- 그랬어요?
- 네, 언제 갔었어요?
-You did?
-Yeah. When were you there?
- 팔십...
- 9년?
-Eighty..
-Nine?
3년이오
Three.
13살 때 거길 갔다구?
I was 13?
- 어쨌든 등산을 하는데...
- 나 등산 좋아해요!
-So anyway, I was hiking..
-I love hiking!
잘됐네요!
That's great!
티비대보 산을 올라가고 있는데...
I was hiking along the foothills
of Mount Tibidaybo..
- 티비다보예요
- 당신이 얘기할래요?
-I think it's "Tibidabo."
-Do you want to tell the story?
웬일이야? 데이트는 어땠어?
How'd your date go?
잘됐어, 나 지금 길 건너에서
섹스하고 있어
Great. I'm across the street
having sex right now.
- 네 얘기 형편없어
- 네가 제대로 얘길 안 해서 그래
-Your story sucks.
-Then you didn't tell it right.
- 어떻게 했나 보여줘봐
- 싫어, 안 해
-Show me how you did it.
-No, I don't want to.
- 여자 알몸 본 게 언제라구?
- 서유럽으로 배낭 여행을 갔어
-How long since you seen a girl naked?
-I was backpacking..
- 느낌이 안 와
- 바르셀로나 교외에서 등산을...
-I'm not feeling it.
-I was outside Barcelona, hiking..
- 달아오르질 않아, 넌 달아올라?
- 6개월이야, 늘 달아올라있다구
-Ross, I'm not hot. Are you hot?
-It's been six months. I'm always hot.
네 얘기엔 설득력이 없어
거짓말인 게 티가 난다구
You're not selling the story.
You don't believe it.
난 지금 데이트 가야 돼
이렇게 한번 해봐
I gotta go, I got a date.
But try this.
내가 오디션 보기 전에
하는 걸 하는 거야
Do what I do before an audition.
나 배 안 고파
I'm not hungry.
그게 아냐
No.
내 카메라로 널 촬영한 다음
어디가 잘못됐나 보라구
Use my camera to record yourself
and see what you're doing wrong.
알았어
I'll try that.
자, 다 세팅해놨으니까
버튼만 눌러, 행운을 빌어
Now, you're all set up. Good to go.
Just hit record. Good luck.
여자랑 관련해서 문제 생기면
그땐 내가 널 도와줄게
If you ever have any problem with the
ladies, you know I'll help you out.
목이 메인다
That means a lot to me, man.
뭐 필요한 거 없어?
렌즈 세척제? 배터리 충분해?
Can I get you anything?
Lens cleaner? Your battery okay?
로스, 마침 여기 있었구나
나 좀 도와줘
Ross, thank God you're here.
You have to help me.
혼잣말하고 있었어?
Were you talking to yourself?
그쪽이 덜 창피하네
맞아, 그랬어
That's less embarrassing.
Yes. Yes, I was.
레이첼이 들어왔을 때
카메라는 완전 잊고 말았어
When she came in,
I totally forgot about the camera.
그렇게 해서 다 녹화된 거라구
It kept rolling
and recorded everything.
우리가 그걸 봐야겠어
Yeah, we're gonna need
to see that tape.
기막힌 생각이네! 레이첼이
얼씨구나 용서해주겠어
What a great idea!
That'll get Rachel to forgive me.
자연 다큐멘터리 보는 거랑
똑같을 텐데 뭐
Come on, it'll be like watching
the Discovery Channel..
아는 원숭이가
나온다는 것만 빼곤 말야
only we'll know the monkeys.
이봐, 절대로 보여줄 수 없어
Look, I'm not gonna let you guys
watch us.
- 나도 아직 못 봤다구
- 내 섹스 테이프 2개랑 교환해
-I haven't even seen it yet.
-I'll trade you two tapes of me having sex.
고맙지만 됐어
Thanks, I'm good.
야한 장면 나오는 건 안 볼게
We don't wanna see the dirty stuff..
- 누가 시작했는지만 볼 거야
- 싫어, 레이첼이 날 죽일 거야
-just the stuff leading up to it.
-No. Rachel's gonna kill me as it is.
이건 레이첼에게 옳지 않아
테이프는 잊어버려
It's not fair to her.
Let's forget the tape.
고마워
Thank you.
- 안 돼
- 당연하지
-No.
-You're right.
- 조이, 안 돼
- 안되고말고
-Joey, no.
-Loud and clear.
왜 틀린 번호를 가르쳐줬는지
이해가 안 돼
I don't get why
they'd give us a fake number.
그 사람들 제정신이었으면
이름도 가짜로 가르쳐줬을걸
If they knew what they were doing,
they didn't give you real names.
전화번호라면 몰라도
이름 갖고 그러는 사람은 없어
Maybe people give out fake numbers,
but not fake names.
안녕, 켄 아담스입니다
반가워요
Hi. Ken Adams.
Nice to meet you.
레지나 펄랜지예요
Regina Phalange.
- 우린 실수한 거 없어
- 그러게 말야
-We didn't do anything wrong.
-I know.
자기 농담이 많이
썰렁하긴 했지만 말야
Although you did tell
an awful lot of jokes.
아깐 재밌었다며?
유머, 유머, 유머!
You said they were funny.
Joke, joke, joke!
유머, 유머...
Joke, joke..
- 당신 질문 때문이야
- 내 질문이 뭐?
-It was your questions.
-What about them?
엄청 퍼부어 댔잖아
배트맨에 나오는 리들러 같았어
The sheer volume.
It was like flying with the Riddler.
- 그거 농담이야?
- 그거 질문이야?
-Was that another joke?
-Was that another question?
로스 아직 여기 있어?
Is Ross still here?
조심해, 누가 곧
질문을 퍼부어 댈 거야
Watch out, honey.
Someone else is asking questions now.
없어, 그런데 얘길 들어봤는데
로스가 실수로 그런 거더라구
No, but he told us what happened.
It was an honest mistake.
너랑 내가 섹스하는 걸
내가 녹화했다면 어떻겠어?
How would you like it if I had sex
with you and I taped it?
관둬
Oh, forget it.
저기 오네, 우리 아기의 아빠
웨스트 빌리지의 포르노 왕
There he is, the father of my child,
the porn king of the West Village.
사고였다구, 알겠어?
It was an accident, okay?
미안하게 생각해
테이프는 보지도 않았다구
I feel bad.
I swear, I didn't even watch it.
자, 받아
Anyway, here.
직접 없애면 기분이 나아질 거야
You might be more comfortable
destroying it yourself.
고마워
Thank you.
뭐라구?
What?
- 보고 싶다는 건 아니겠지?
- 당연히 보고 싶지!
-You don't want to see this, do you?
-Hell, yeah!
이건 절대로 보여줄 수가 없어
I am not gonna show you this.
섹스하는 데 말고
누가 시작했나만 확인해
Not the sex part.
Just the stuff leading up to it.
포기해, 없앨 거야
Forget it.
알았어, 알았다구, 궁금증을
날려버릴 방법을 찾아볼게
We'll think of another way to put the
"who came on to who" thing to rest.
방법을 찾아, 어서!
Come on now, think!
다 관둬, 이건 레이첼 거야
맘대로 처분할 권리가 있다구
It's Rachel's tape,
and she can do whatever she wants.
레이첼은 없애길 원해
그러니 얘긴 여기서 끝내
And she wants to destroy it,
so end of story.
- 테이프를 보고 싶어
- 뭐라구?
-I want to see it.
-What?
이걸 못 보게 하려고 안달인데
You don't want us to see this.
나도 보여주긴 싫지만 네가 너무
과민하게 나오니 보고 싶어졌어
You so badly don't want us to see it
that it makes me want to see it.
보는 거야, 마는 거야?
Are we watching the tape or not?
- 다 널 위해서 그런 거야
- 그 말은 신뢰가 안 가네
-It's for your sake.
-I don't believe you.
네가 애걸하는 걸
보여주기 싫어서겠지
I think you don't want them
to see you begging me.
- 레이첼, 부탁이야
- 예고편 나왔네
-Rachel, please?
-Oh, a little preview.
좋아, 대신 내가 신사의 도리를
지키려고 했다는 것만 알아줘
Fine. I want the record to show
that I tried to take the high road.
왜냐하면 5분 후엔 이럴 거거든
Because in about five minutes,
I'm gonna be saying..
자, 시작한다
Okay, here we go.
너무 행복해
I'm so happy.
여기 있었구나, 나 좀 도와줘
혼잣말하고 있었어?
Thank God you're here. Help me.
Were you talking to yourself?
- 나 나왔어
- 임신하게 된대요
-There I am.
-You're gonna get pregnant.
나 큰일났어
I screwed up so bad.
청첩장 보낸다고 모니카한테
말한게 몇 주 전이거든
I told Monica that I'd send
those wedding invitations weeks ago.
안보냈어?
You didn't do it?
사무실 책상 안에 넣어두곤
오늘까지 깜박했지 뭐야
I put them in my desk at work,
and forgot about them until today.
괜찮아, 손님들 모두
결혼식에 왔잖아, 난 괜찮아
Sweetie, it's okay. Everybody made it
to the wedding. I'm fine.
- 그런데 손이 좀 아프네
- 알아
-Kind of hurting my hand though.
-I know.
모니카가 얼마나 볶아댔는데
정신을 못 차렸다니...
I can 't believe it, especially after
Monica went on and on about it.
"청첩장 여기 있어, 레이첼
조심해야 돼, 레이첼"
"Here are the invitations, Rachel.
Be very careful, Rachel.
"뭐 마실 땐 청첩장에서
멀리 떨어져, 레이첼"
Please, drinking no liquids
around the invitations, Rachel."
청첩장 위에 누워서 한 거야?
Did you do it on our invitations?
발송된 청첩장은 아냐
Not on the ones we sent out.
그럼 틀에 끼우라고
되돌려준 청첩장이군
So just the ones you gave back to us
and we had framed?
믿을 수가 없어, 둘이 약혼한 게
엊그제 같은데 말야
It seems like yesterday
they just got engaged.
그러게 말야
I know.
둘이 약혼하던 날 생각나?
너랑 나랑 하마터면...
Remember the night they got engaged?
How you and I almost..
기억하고말고
Oh, I remember how we almost.
그때 방해꾼이 없었다면
끝까지 갔을까?
You think we would've
gone through with it?
끝까지 갔을 것 같아?
You think we would have done it?
난 하고 싶었어
넌 어땠는지 몰라도 말야
I know I wanted to.
I just wasn 't sure if you did.
나도 하고 싶었어
Oh, I wanted to.
그러니까 우리 둘 다 원했구나
So we both wanted to.
재미있네
Interesting.
어쨌든 최선인 쪽으로
일이 풀렸으리라 믿어
Anyway, it probably worked out
for the best.
그럼
Yeah, sure.
10초 있다 로스가 키스할 거야
In about 10 seconds, he kisses me.
5초 있다 내가 왜 그랬나가 나와
In about 5 seconds, you'll see why.
내가 서유럽으로 배낭 여행
갔었던 얘기 너한테 해줬어?
Did I ever tell you about the time
I backpacked through Western Europe?
이제 곧 애걸하는 게 나올 거야
Get ready to see some begging.
- 네가 먼저 시작했구나!
- 뭐라구?
-Oh, you came on to Ross!
-What?
너무 행복해
Now I'm so happy.
- 무슨 소리야?
- 유럽 얘길 써먹었잖아!
-What?
-You used the Europe story!
그건 섹스하고 싶을 때 쓰는
마법의 주문이라구!
That's the magic story you use
when you want to have sex!
- 너희들이 그 얘길 어떻게 알아?
- 너야말로 그 얘길 어떻게 알아?
-How do you know about that story?
아이린이 어떤 남자한테
들었다며 얘기해줬어
My friend Irene heard it
from some guy.
어떤 남자!
Some guy!
아냐, 아이린 말이
켄 아담스라는 남자랬어
No, she told me that
his name was Ken Adams.
켄 아담스!
Ken Adams!
다들 유럽 얘길 알고 있나 봐?
So, people are familiar
with the Europe story?
누가 먼저 시작했냐 하는 건
중요하지 않아
About that, the "who came on to who"
thing really doesn't matter.
어쨌든 일어날 일이었으니까
It would have happened either way.
네가 시작 안 했으면
내가 했을 거야
If you hadn't initiated it,
I know I would have.
- 멋진 밤이었어
- 그래, 그랬어
-It was an amazing night.
-It was. It was amazing.
멋져 보였어?
You think it looked amazing?
나도 몰라, 정말로 안 봤거든
I don't know.
I honestly didn't watch it.
나도
Yeah, me neither.
아직은
Yet.
- 좀 이상할 텐데
- 맞아, 그럴 거야
-That may be weird.
-Yeah, it would be really weird.
- 행운을 빌어
- 너야말로
-Good luck.
-Good luck to you.
- 소리 제거해도 돼?
- 물론이지
-Mind if I mute?
-Oh, please.
- 옷 벗고 있어
- 너 참 빨리도 벗는다
-There go the clothes.
-You are undressing awfully quickly.
6개월이야, 레이첼
6개월이라구
Six months, Rachel. Six months.
- 둘이 멋있네
- 그 말하려고 했어
-We look pretty good.
-I was gonna say.
- 선탠이 멋있어
- 고마워
-Nice tan.
-Thank you.
바로 전주 주말에 해변에 갔었어
I'd just gone to
the beach that weekend.
- 계속 운동한 거야?
- 그랬다니까
-Have you been working out?
-I have been working out.
생각했던 것보다 훨씬...
This is so much better
than I ever..
너무 이상해
Oh, that's not pretty.
- 그만 꺼, 어서
- 안 돼! 안 돼!
-Make it stop. Make it stop.
-Oh, no!
적어준 전화번호랑 완전히 달라
Greg and Jenny's number
is totally different in here.
- 내가 그렇게 질문이 많아?
- 아니
-I don't ask too many questions, do I?
-No.
- 정말?
- 그렇다니까
-Really?
-Absolutely not.
- 정말?
- 내가 미쳐
-Really?
-Oh, God.
착오가 있었던 게 분명해
전화를 해봐야겠어
I bet that phone thing was some sort
of mix-up. I'm gonna call them.
여보세요, 그렉?
비행기에서 만난 모니카예요
Hello, Greg?
This is Monica from the plane.
당신이 준 전화번호가 853국에...
Listen, the number that
you gave me, 8-5-3..
제니가 옛날 번호를 가르쳐줬대!
Jenny's been giving out
their old number!
제니도 참! 진짜로 참 제니답네!
Jenny! That is so Jenny!
다음 주 토요일에 시간 있어요?
How would you like to
get together next Saturday?
좋아요, 그럼 일요일은요?
Okay, how about Sunday?
좋아요, 그럼 다다음주는요?
Okay, the week after that?
다다다음주는요?
The week after that?
이봐요, 우린 적절한 질문만 하는
재밌고 흥미진진한 사람들이에요
You know what? We are interesting,
funny people with good questions.
우리의 진면목을 보지 못하고...
And if you and your precious Jenny
can't see that..
1월 15일이요?
January 15?
그럼 그때 봐요!
We'll see you then!